<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The 26th Conference of the International Linear Algebra Society on ILAS2025</title><link>https://ilas2025.tw/</link><description>Recent content in The 26th Conference of the International Linear Algebra Society on ILAS2025</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 14:45:12 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ilas2025.tw/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Student support</title><link>https://ilas2025.tw/registration/student-support/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 14:45:12 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://ilas2025.tw/registration/student-support/</guid><description>ILAS welcomes and encourages students to attend the ILAS conference. For this purpose, the society offers two types of support for PhD students.
Registration fee-waiver Travel / accommodation support up to 700 USD The students who would like to apply for one or both of them should fill in the application form before January 31.
Registration fee-waiver Students can join ILAS for free and benefit from the reduced registration fee.</description></item><item><title>Social events</title><link>https://ilas2025.tw/registration/social/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 19:26:41 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://ilas2025.tw/registration/social/</guid><description>Welcome reception The reception will be held at the conference venue on Monday evening.
Taiwanese delicacies and beverage will be served to welcome the linear algbera community.
Price: included in the registration fee
Excursion The excursion will be held on Wednesday afternoon. There are two options.
Option 1: Cruise tour in Kaoshiung Harbor (limited vacancies) As the largest harbor in Taiwan, Kaohsiung Harbor serves as both an economic and cultural hub.</description></item><item><title>Mini-symposia</title><link>https://ilas2025.tw/program/mini/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 17:04:33 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://ilas2025.tw/program/mini/</guid><description>Mini-symposia Embracing new opportunities in numerical linear algebra
Pengwen Chen, Matthrew Lin Confirmed speakers Dong Bo, Chun-Yueh Chiang, King-Wah Eric Chu, Sean Y S Hon, Akira Imakura, Deflation techniques for matrix function calculations based on double exponential-type numerical integral formula Zhigang Jia, Matrix completion method from compressed sensing to color video inpainting Chiu-Yen Kao, Hao Liu, Shinya Miyajima, Meiyue Shao, Li-Gang (Charles) Lin, Fast SDDRE-based maneuvering-target interception at pre-specified orientation Combinatorial matrix theory</description></item><item><title>Plenary speakers</title><link>https://ilas2025.tw/program/plenary/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 23:15:09 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://ilas2025.tw/program/plenary/</guid><description>Plenary Speakers Haim Avron (Tel Aviv University) SIAG/LA Lecture Dario Bini (Università di Pisa) Hans Schneider Prize Lecture Fan Chung Graham (University of California, San Diego) Fumio Hiai (Tohoku University) Daniel Kressner (EPFL) LAA Lecture Ren-Cang Li (University of Texas at Arlington) Karen Meagher (University of Regina) Polona Oblak (University of Ljubljana) Fernando De Terán Vergara (Universidad Carlos III de Madrid) Karol Życzkowski (Jagiellonian University)</description></item><item><title>LOGO</title><link>https://ilas2025.tw/about/logo/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 23:36:06 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://ilas2025.tw/about/logo/</guid><description>The conference LOGO is inspired by the Great Harbor Bridge, which is a landmark in Kaohsiung featuring its streamlined design. It is also the first bridge that can rotate horizontally to let boats pass through.
If the LOGO is viewed as a graph, then it is the graph with its graph6 string &amp;quot;G?}WNc&amp;quot; . It second smallest Laplacian eigenvalue is 1.6202543669426&amp;hellip;
You may run the Sage code below
g = Graph(&amp;#34;G?</description></item><item><title>Copyright</title><link>https://ilas2025.tw/copyright/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 18:19:42 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://ilas2025.tw/copyright/</guid><description>The website was built by Jephian Lin using Hugo static site generators and Ananke theme.
The photos and images used in this website are from the following resources:
Courtesy of Yu-Ting Chen. Courtesy of Jephian Lin. Wikipedia. Kaohsiung Travel.</description></item><item><title>Local</title><link>https://ilas2025.tw/taiwan/local/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 23:19:29 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://ilas2025.tw/taiwan/local/</guid><description>Kaohsiung Kaohsiung is a big city in southern Taiwan. It is located on the southwest coast and is one of Taiwan&amp;rsquo;s largest cities. Kaohsiung has a population of around 2.7 million people.
The city has a rich history with a former name Takow given by the indigenous people. It was originally a small fishing village many years ago. Over time, it grew into an important port city. Today, Kaohsiung is known for its busy harbor, which is one of the largest in the world.</description></item><item><title>Plan your trip</title><link>https://ilas2025.tw/taiwan/travel/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 23:49:51 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://ilas2025.tw/taiwan/travel/</guid><description>Visa Many countries are eligible for the visa exemption program, with a duration of stay of up to 90 days.
In general, you may follow the instructions of the Bureau of Consular Affairs to apply for a visa.
Airport With fewer flight options, Kaohsiung International Airport (KHH) is the closest airport to the conference venue.
Taiwan Taoyuan International Airport (TPE) is the primary airport of Taiwan and is an important hub in Asia.</description></item><item><title>Welcoming and Inclusiveness Statement</title><link>https://ilas2025.tw/about/inclusiveness-statement/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 15:37:17 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://ilas2025.tw/about/inclusiveness-statement/</guid><description>The ILAS2025 organizing team will adhere to the Welcoming and Inclusiveness Statement of ILAS and make the conference an friendly environment for all.
Welcoming and Inclusiveness Statement The International Linear Algebra Society (ILAS) is comprised of a diverse global membership.
It is the policy of ILAS to offer a welcoming and inclusive environment to all participants in its activities, including all its meetings and conferences, regardless of gender, gender identity or expression, sexual orientation, race, color, national or ethnic origin, religion or religious belief, age, marital status, disabilities, and field of expertise.</description></item></channel></rss>