<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Program on ILAS2025</title><link>https://ilas2025.tw/program/</link><description>Recent content in Program on ILAS2025</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Apr 2023 22:25:46 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ilas2025.tw/program/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Contributed talks and posters</title><link>https://ilas2025.tw/program/contributed-and-poster/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 04:29:42 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://ilas2025.tw/program/contributed-and-poster/</guid><description>The deadline for submitting a contributed talk or a poster is March 31.
Contributed talks To submit a poster. Please visit the registration page to submit the abstract through Upload Abstract.
Within one week, you will receive an email of whether the contributed talk is approved.
After that, you may register the conference.
Posters To submit a poster. Please email ilas2025 [at] math [dot] nsysu [dot] edu [dot] tw the following information:</description></item><item><title>Mini-symposia</title><link>https://ilas2025.tw/program/mini/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 17:04:33 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://ilas2025.tw/program/mini/</guid><description>Mini-symposia Embracing new opportunities in numerical linear algebra
Pengwen Chen, Matthrew Lin Confirmed speakers Dong Bo, TBA King-Wah Eric Chu, TBA Akira Imakura, Deflation techniques for matrix function calculations based on double exponential-type numerical integral formula Zhigang Jia, Matrix completion method from compressed sensing to color video inpainting Chiu-Yen Kao, TBA Matthew M. Lin, TBA Hao Liu, TBA Shinya Miyajima, TBA Meiyue Shao, TBA Li-Gang (Charles) Lin, Fast SDDRE-based maneuvering-target interception at pre-specified orientation Combinatorial matrix theory</description></item><item><title>Plenary speakers</title><link>https://ilas2025.tw/program/plenary/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 23:15:09 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://ilas2025.tw/program/plenary/</guid><description>Plenary Speakers Haim Avron (Tel Aviv University) SIAG/LA Lecture Dario Bini (Università di Pisa) Hans Schneider Prize Lecture Fan Chung Graham (University of California, San Diego) Fumio Hiai (Tohoku University) Daniel Kressner (EPFL) LAA Lecture Ren-Cang Li (University of Texas at Arlington) Karen Meagher (University of Regina) Polona Oblak (University of Ljubljana) Fernando De Terán Vergara (Universidad Carlos III de Madrid) LAMA Lecture Karol Życzkowski (Jagiellonian University)</description></item></channel></rss>